Guide to the Leadership Education at Duke Divinity Records, 1999-2010, undated UA.19.06.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Leadership Education at Duke Divinity Records
1999-2010, undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University. Divinity School
UA.19.06.0001
25 Linear Feet
Leadership Education at Duke Divinity provides educational services, intellectual resources, and facilitates networks of institutions influencing Christian institutional leadership. Leadership Education at Duke Divinity School Records contain correspondence, memoranda, research, and reports related to the Pulpit and Pew research project; Forum on Excellence/Advancing Pastoral Excellence Initiative project; Duke Youth Academy; and the website for national Sustaining Pastoral Excellence projects.
Biographical / Historical
Leadership Education at Duke Divinity (LEDD) provides educational services, intellectual resources, and facilitates networks of institutions influencing Christian institutional leadership. Founded by a grant from the Lilly Endowment Inc. in 2008, LEDD is part of the Duke Divinity School and offers programs and grants for Christian leaders.
The Pulpit & Pew was a research project designed to describe the state of Protestant and Catholic pastoral leadership in the U.S. The project examined trends facing clergy and aimed to provide resources for pastoral leadership.
The Duke Divinity School coordinated the Sustaining Pastoral Excellence program under the Advancing Pastoral Excellence initiative. In May of 2005, it hosted a major Forum on Excellence in Ministry in Indianapolis, which brought together 250 leaders from a variety of churches and church-related settings.
The Duke Youth Academy was designed as a year-long program for young people to explore Christian life. The week-long residency on the Duke University campus was combined with a year of mentorship, practice, and online community.
The website for Sustaining Pastoral Excellence projects served as a forum for articles and nationwide projects nationwide from 2005 to 2008, when publication ceased.
The Institute for Clergy Excellence was funded by the Lilly Endowment for the Duke Divinity School to host a coordination program enabling grantees to connect with and learn from one another.
Access Restrictions
Access restricted. For a period of twenty-five years from the origin of the material, permission in writing from the office of origin and the University Archivist is required for use of administrative records. After twenty-five years, records that have been processed may be consulted with the permission of the University Archivist. Contact Research Services for more information.
Access note. Collection contains fragile audiovisual/photographic formats that may need to be reformatted before use. Contact Research Services for access.
Provenance
The Leadership Education at Duke Divinity Records were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a transfer from Mary Page, Events Management and Support Services, Duke Divinity School in 2016.
Related Materials
Duke Divinity School Records.
University Archives, Duke University.
Collection Overview
The collection contains correspondence, memoranda, research, and reports related to the Pulpit and Pew research project; Forum on Excellence/Advancing Pastoral Excellence Initiative project; Duke Youth Academy; and the website for national Sustaining Pastoral Excellence projects.
Duke University -- Administration; Duke University -- Students; Duke University. School of Religion; Duke University -- Faculty; Duke University. Divinity School; Education, Higher -- Religious aspects; Students -- Religion
- Accession UA2016-0006, 1999-2010 and undated
  Conditions Governing Access
  Access restricted. For a period of twenty-five years from the origin of the material, permission in writing from the office of origin and the University Archivist is required for use of administrative records. After twenty-five years, records that have been processed may be consulted with the permission of the University Archivist. Contact Research Services for more information.
  Access note. Collection contains fragile audiovisual/photographic formats that may need to be reformatted before use. Contact Research Services for access.
  - Pulpit and Pew Research Project, 1999-2005, undated
    Scope and Contents
    Includes correspondence, memoranda, research, and reports related to the Pulpit and Pew research project.
    - Church Leaders Group, 2001 (Box 1)
      Administrative records restricted until 2026.
    - Church Leaders Meeting, 2000 April (Box 1)
      Administrative records restricted until 2025.
    - Possible Research Topics, 2000 April (Box 1)
    - Church Leaders Group Meeting, 2000 November (Box 1)
    - Church Leaders Meeting, 2000 November (Box 1)
    - Core Seminar Meeting (St. Paul, MN), 2000 October (Box 1)
    - Core Seminar Meeting (Durham, NC), 2001 August 22-24 (Box 1)
    - Core Seminar Meeting, 2002 February (Box 1)
      Administrative records restricted until 2027.
    - Core Seminar Meeting, 2000 October 26-28 (Box 1)
    - Theology Conservatory, 2001 January (Box 1)
    - Lilly Project Core Seminar, undated (Box 1)
    - Core Seminar (Durham), 2000 February (Box 1)
    - Chicago, undated (Box 1)
    - Bolan, 2002 (Box 1)
    - Parr, undated (Box 1)
    - Dissertation Competition, undated (Box 1)
    - Ormand Center Pastoral Leadership Project Dissertation Fellowships, 2002 (Box 1)
    - National Federation of Priests Council, undated (Box 1)
    - Survey Endorsement Letters, undated (Box 1)
    - Post Doctoral Fellowship, undated (Box 1)
    - Lee, Virginia A. Ormond Center Post Doc. Fellowship, 1999 February (Box 1)
      Administrative records restricted until 2024.
    - Limbo, Ernest M. Ormand Center Post Doc. Fellowship, 1999 February (Box 1)
    - Final Proposal Package, 1999 September (Box 1)
    - Theological Education, undated (Box 1)
    - Bibliography and (annotated), undated (Box 1)
    - Clergy Couples, undated (Box 1)
    - Clergy Ethics, undated (Box 1)
    - Clergy Families, undated (Box 1)
    - News Stories, undated (Box 1)
    - Dick Wills, 2000 March (Box 1)
    - Methodist Projects, undated (Box 1)
    - Survey Materials Questionnaires/Instruments, undated (Box 1)
    - Good Ministry Papers, 2002 (Box 1)
    - Credo Project Episcopal /Fenhagen, undated (Box 1)
    - Disciples of Christ, undated (Box 1)
    - PCUSA "Crisis and Leadership", undated (Box 1)
    - PCUSA "Pastor Shortage", undated (Box 1)
    - Entering Student Questionnaire, undated (Box 1)
    - Episcopal/Zaccheus, undated (Box 1)
    - Murnion "Leadership", undated (Box 1)
    - Project Update, 2001 January (Box 1)
    - Financial Report, 2002 (Box 1)
    - Dissemination Grant Year 1 Financial, 2003 March (Box 1)
      Administrative records restricted until 2028.
    - Revised Budget, 2002 December (Box 1)
    - Consultations, undated (Box 1)
    - Consultation, 1999 April (Box 1)
    - Consultant Meetings, 1999 April-May (Box 1)
    - Ministry Consultation, 1999 May (Box 1)
    - Consultation Notes, 1999 May (Box 1)
    - Jewish Theological Advisory Committee, undated (Box 1)
    - Other Ministry Projects, undated (Box 1)
    - Cass Dale, undated (Box 1)
    - Pastor Care, undated (Box 1)
    - Survey Firms (Gallop, etc.), undated (Box 1)
    - Dick Hunt/Fuller, undated (Box 1)
    - Survey, undated (Box 1)
    - Leadership Letters, undated (Box 1)
    - Ministry Project Summary, undated (Box 1)
    - Lilly Ministry Programs, undated (Box 1)
    - Hispanic Clergy, undated (Box 1)
    - Ministry Advisory Committee, undated (Box 1)
    - Hess, undated (Box 1)
    - Excellence in Ministry, undated (Box 1)
    - Leadership, undated (Box 1)
    - Coppel, 2001-2002 (Box 1)
    - Kolbet, Paul, undated (Box 1)
    - Jones, Kenneth, undated (Box 1)
    - The Congregation Advisor Meeting WETA, 2003 (Box 1)
    - Hahnenberg, Edward, undated (Box 1)
    - Brotzman, undated (Box 1)
    - Bolger, 2001-2002 (Box 1)
    - Pulpit and Pew Pastoral Leadership, 2000 January 1-2004 December 31 (Box 1)
      Administrative records restricted until 2029.
    - NFPC Study Proposal "Recently Ordained", undated (Box 2)
    - Alban Contract and Publishing, undated (Box 2)
    - Publications Correspondence, Pulpit and Pew, undated (Box 2)
    - Eric Gottesman (photographer), undated (Box 2)
    - CCGI-Mark Constantine, undated (Box 2)
    - Patty Chang, undated (Box 2)
    - Cross Com/Don Shin, undated (Box 2)
    - NFPC, undated (Box 2)
    - Pulpit and Pew Dis. Fellows, 2001 November (Box 2)
    - Curtis, 2001-2002 (Box 2)
    - Daily, Eileen, undated (Box 2)
    - Carbine, Rosemary, undated (Box 2)
    - Pullen, 2001-2002 (Box 2)
    - McQueeney, 2001-2002 (Box 2)
    - Summative Conference Materials Packet, 2004 February (Box 2)
    - American Baptist Seminary West, undated (Box 2)
    - Steven Berry, Doctoral Research Assistant, undated (Box 2)
    - Doctor Alan C. Klass, President, Change Mentoring, Inc., undated (Box 2)
    - Larry Mamiya, undated (Box 2)
    - Leadership Materials Theory and Stories, undated (Box 2)
    - Clergy Salaries, undated (Box 2)
    - Clergy/Lay Conflict, undated (Box 2)
    - Drop Out/Retention Study Hoge Proposal, undated (Box 2)
    - Clergy Women, undated (Box 2)
    - Rolf Menning, undated (Box 2)
    - Priests, undated (Box 2)
    - Neo Institutionalism, undated (Box 2)
    - Salaries, undated (Box 2)
    - Salary Study, undated (Box 2)
    - Sexuality/Homosexuality, undated (Box 2)
    - Theological Education, undated (Box 2)
    - Clergy Status/Prestige, undated (Box 2)
    - Ed Lehman DPLP File, undated (Box 2)
    - Moral, undated (Box 2)
    - Protestant Clergy (overview studies), undated (Box 2)
    - Nazarene Research, undated (Box 2)
    - Call to Ministry, undated (Box 2)
    - Careers (miscellaneous papers), undated (Box 2)
    - Catholics, undated (Box 2)
    - Hispanic/Adventists, undated (Box 2)
    - Supply and Demand Careers-Patti Chang, undated (Box 2)
    - Vital Congregations (Wilker, et. al.), undated (Box 2)
    - National Church Lists, undated (Box 2)
    - Alban Contract, undated (Box 2)
    - Scott Appleby Article, undated (Box 2)
    - Matthew Price, "what we know about x", undated (Box 2)
    - Paul Wilkes/Boston Globe, undated (Box 2)
    - Clergy Compensation Study (Becky and Matthew), undated (Box 2)
    - Chronicle of Higher Education: Piece on Theology Students, undated (Box 2)
    - Ecclesiology/Theology, undated (Box 2)
    - Families with (clergies), undated (Box 2)
    - Researchers (potential), undated (Box 2)
    - Lay Pastoral Leadership, undated (Box 2)
    - Clergy and Media Study Joyce Smith, undated (Box 2)
    - Catholic University Sub-Contractor/Hoge, undated (Box 2)
    - Adair Lummis, undated (Box 2)
    - Applicants, 2000 (Box 2)
    - Leadership Survey Pre-Test, undated (Box 2)
    - DPLP Summaries, undated (Box 2)
    - Communication/Publicity, undated (Box 3)
    - Dean Hoge, undated (Box 3)
    - Don Miller, undated (Box 3)
    - Sociology of Religion, undated (Box 3)
    - Correspondence, undated (Box 3)
    - Alan Klass Proposal, undated (Box 3)
    - Lehman Mss, undated (Box 3)
    - US Congregation (Presbyterian), undated (Box 3)
    - Klass "When Pastors are Fired", undated (Box 3)
    - Research Abstracts, undated (Box 3)
    - News Releases, 2003 (Box 3)
    - District Superindency Report, undated (Box 3)
    - Survey Hard Copies, undated (Box 3)
    - Survey Questions National Australia US Congregations, undated (Box 3)
    - Church Leadership Group Nominees, undated (Box 3)
    - NFPC Reports, undated (Box 3)
    - Larry Witham Correspondence, undated (Box 3)
    - Project Planning Materials Browning Program Lilly Meeting, 1999 August (Box 3)
    - Advisory Committee, undated (Box 3)
    - Planning Grant Proposal, undated (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Daniel Aleshire, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
      Administrative records restricted until 2030.
    - Forum Participants: Joy Anderson, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Edwin David Aponte, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Kevin R. Armstrong, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Msgr. Arturo J. Banuelas, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Dorothy Bass, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Dr. Michel Battle, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Timothy A. Beach-Verhey, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Ronald Beauchamp, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Woody Bedell, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Gail E. Bowman, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Chris Braudaway-Bauman, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: J. Elise Brown, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Lynn Bujnak, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Jacqueline Burton, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Dr. Francis JK. Butler, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Kathleen A. Callahan, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Cynthia M. Campbell, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Kenneth Carder, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Jackson W. Carroll, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Michael G. Cartwright, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Karen Chakoian, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Mark Chaves, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Marsha Clark Myers, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Raymond Clothier, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Dr. Christopher Coble, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Justin Coleman, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Mark D. Constantine, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Martin B. Kopenhager, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Scott Cormode, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Carol Cotton Winn, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: David D. Cunningham, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Kenda Creasy Dean, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Lillian Daniel, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Dr. Tom Dendy, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Susan P. Dickerman, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Larry Dill, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: The Rev. David Dragseth, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Gonzalo Duarte, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Michael F. Duffy, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Craig Dykstra, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Kim Maphis Early, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: James Kenneth Echols, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Fred Edie, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Rev. Chris Enstad, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Kenneth Eriks, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Peg Falls-Corbitt, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Mary Jo Flory-Steury, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Lucy A. Forster-Smith, The Rev. Dr., 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Mark Foglesong, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Charussey L. Gillett, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Dr. Lewis F. Galloway, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Rev. Terry Menefee Gau, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: James M. Goodman, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Deirdre W. Gordon, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Stephen R. Graham, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Thomas H. Graves, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Gary Gunderson, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: David Guthrie, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Jerry Haas, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Bruce M. Hartung, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Kate Harvey, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Faith Kirkham Hawkins, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Pamela C. Hawkins, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Trace Hawthorne, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: James Heft, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Douglas A. Hicks, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Samuel Hogan, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Dean Hoge, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: E. Brooks Holifield, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: David Horn, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Robert T. Hoshibata, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Lucinda Huffaker, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Bishop Janice Riggle Huie, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Brenda G. Husson, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: John James, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Michael Jenkins, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Rev. Mary Eleanor Johns (Ellie), 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Susan B. W. Johnson, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Sue Joyner, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: L. Gregory Jones, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Susan Pendleton Jones, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Jeff Kaster, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Susan Kendall, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Alexander Levering Kern, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: J. Cletus Kiley, Rev., 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Christa Kline, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Kathryn Kleinhans, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Scott Klemsz, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Victor Klimoski, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Rev. Ronald Knott, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Courtney Krueger, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: William H. Lamar 4th (Bill), 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Thomas N. Landy, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Martha Lang, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Clarence Langdon, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Rev. Dr. James B Lemler, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Jim Lewis, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Steven Lewis, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Lowell W. Livezey, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Tom Lock, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Rev. Patricia Lowell, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Carole Lytch, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Mary Frances Malone, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: W. Joseph Mann (Joe), 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Penny Long Marler, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Rev. Harold E. Masbock 3rd, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: George A Mason, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Fumitaka Matsuoka, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Janet Maykus, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: David Mcallister Wilson, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: John E McKoy, Dr., 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: William Meyer, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Mark Miller-Mclemore, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Roberto Miranda, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Michael Mooty, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Rev. Mary Ann Moman, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Dwight Moody, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: Lynda Morgan-Clement, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 3)
    - Forum Participants: G.K. Scott Morris, MD, Mdiv, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Susan M. Mountain, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Russ S. Moxley, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: James Nieman, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: L. Roger Owens, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Rev. Fred Oakes, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: David L. Odom, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Mark R. Orten, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Michael Palmer, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Dr. Jeri Parris, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Michael Peterson, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Carol Pinkham Oak, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Christine D. Pohle, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Riess Potterveld, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: David S. Price, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Lee Ramsey, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Mark R. Ramseth, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Graham Reeside, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Rev. Lisa D. Rhoades, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Nancy Rich, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Bernard L. Richardson, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Dawn C. Richter, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Mary Jo Flory-Steury, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Prince Rainy Rivers, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Michael Roberts, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Dr. Shirley J. Roels, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: David Rohrer, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Rev. Dr. Patrick Russell, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Chris Scharen, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Matthew Schlimm, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Katrina Schuth, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: A. Craig Settlegg, Rev., 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Tim Shapiro, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Deann Shorb, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Gary Shorb, CEO, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Sheldon W. Sorge, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Rev. Robert J. Silva, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Clay Smith, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Kevin Spears, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Harvey Stalwick, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Bryan Stone, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Jonathan Strandjord, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Ann Svennungsen, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Lynn Szwaja, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Murphy M. Thomas, Ph.D., 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Fredrica Thompsett, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: David Tide, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Craig D. Townsend, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Cheryl Tupper, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Karen Turner, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Janice Virtue, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Rev. John J. Wall, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Mac Warford, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Lovett H. Weems Jr., 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Susan M. Weber, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Jacqueline Wanger, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Bob Wells, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Barbara G. Wheeler, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Melissa Wiginton, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: John Wimmer, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: James P. Wind, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Jacqueline M. Witter, ED.D., 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: John D. Witvliet, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: David J. Wood, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)